(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T01:11:40.348767",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The night shines brighter when she sings...
Special guests are here to join the fun, so don't blink
The moment we've all been waiting for...
こんなことになるなんて
If I had known it would come to this,
出会う前にわかってたら
before we even met...
もう少しだけちゃんとした僕を
I should have been able to show you
見せられたはずなんだ
a slightly more put-together me.
どうしたらいいのかなって
Wondering what I should do,
頭ではわかってるけど
I know it in my head, but...
何気ないちょっとした言葉で
A casual, little word
嬉しい顔が出えちゃって
makes a happy expression slip out.
こんなバレバレじゃカッコ悪いな
Being this obvious is so uncool,
でもこのままじゃ引き下がれないよな
but I can't back down like this.
でもいざ向かうと照れくさくて
Yet when the moment comes, I get too shy,
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
and I just can't say "I love you."
この気持ち伝わるかな
Will these feelings reach you?
浮き足立って空回り
Getting carried away and spinning my wheels,
何も言えずまたサヨナラ
saying nothing, and saying goodbye again.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you way too much, it's unbearable.
明日こそは言えるかな
Can I finally say it tomorrow?
あなたも僕と同じように恋してたら…なんて考えてるんだ
Wondering if you're in love just like me...
会えない日が続いている
Even if I know it's no use thinking about it,
このままじゃよろしくない
it still hurts just the same.
あっさところで何ができるって
What can I even do at a time like this?
わけじゃないんだけど
It's a once-in-a-lifetime kind of love.
こんな恋は二度とないな
I know that well enough,
頭ではわかってるけど
yet your dazzling smile makes me panic.
眩しすぎるその笑顔が
Wanting to gaze at you forever,
僕を焦らせるんだ
while also wanting to look away...
ずっと見ていたくなるような
I wonder if you understand this feeling.
目をそしたくなってしまうような
If you're smiling, that's enough for me,
こんな気持ちわかるのかな
though I'd rather be the one by your side.
あなたが笑ってるならそれでいいんだけど
Maybe, just maybe, you've known all along?
でも隣は僕がいいなあ
I love you way too much, it's unbearable.
もしかしたら実はづっと気づいてるんじゃないかな
Can I finally say it tomorrow?
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I could never say anything so dramatic,
明日こそは言えるかな
but I just can't hold back these feelings.
全てをひっくり返すくらいの
Ever since the day I met you,
臭いセリフは言えそうにないが…
my feelings haven't changed at all.
どうしたってこの気持ちは抑えられそうにはないんだ
I love you so much, it hurts.
あなたと出会ったあの日からずっと気持ちは変わらないけど
Will today be the day I tell you?
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
Even if we're apart, I want you to know
この気持ち伝わるかな
that my heart beats only for you.
浮き足立って空回り 何も言えずまたサヨナラ
I love you more than words can say.
なに言えるかな
What can I say?
地面をひっくり返すくらいの いきなセリフは言えそうにないや
I don't think I can say anything suave enough to flip the world upside down.
アナタに出会ったあの日から
Ever since the day I met you,
どうしたってこの気持ちは抑えられそうにはないんだ
no matter what, I just can't seem to hold back these feelings.
アナタと出会ったあの日からずっと気持ちは変わらないけど
Ever since the day I met you, my feelings haven't changed, but...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです この気持ち伝わるかな
I can't say "I like you." I wonder if this feeling will reach you?
躓いたってから回り 何も言えずまたさよなら
Stumbling and spinning in circles, unable to say anything, it's goodbye again.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです 明日こそは言い出せるかな
I love you so much I can't stand it. Will I be able to say it tomorrow?
アナタも僕と同じように恋してたらなんて考えてる
I wonder if you're falling in love just like me, as I sit and think about it.
でもわかってる 考えすぎてこと
But I know I'm overthinking things.
Mobo mobo! Kobo Kanaeru's 3D birthday stream!
Mobo mobo! Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D birthday stream!
Hi everyone, konbo! Kobo kana iru desu!
Hi everyone, konbo! It's Kobo Kanaeru!
Kobo no 3D seita haishin yokoso!
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D birthday stream 2025! Pochi pochi pochi!
How was Kobo's performance? Mmm? Doudatta? Mata gita dettekita yo ne?
How was Kobo's performance? Hm? How was it? I brought out the guitar again, right?
Chotto matte... let me put the guitar down first.
Hold on a second... let me put the guitar down first.
Okay!
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream 2025! Kobo no 3D seita haishin yokoso!
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream 2025! Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an... um... idol mitai konzato... um... event?
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an... um... idol-like concert... um... event?
3D birthday stream for about an hour with a lot of amazing and awesome guests, I bet you guys can't wait!
A 3D birthday stream for about an hour with lots of amazing and awesome guests. I bet you guys can't wait!
Hey Kobo, your stage is different! Oh, chat, nice ice chat, you noticed it!
"Hey Kobo, your stage is different!" Oh, chat, nice eye chat, you noticed it!
Yeah, you're right, look at Kobo's new stage! Dekai!
Yeah, you're right, look at Kobo's new stage! It's huge!
New stage! There's a big... chirus right here... oki na chirus...
A new stage! There's a big... clouds right here... big clouds...
And so many stars! Stars! So many stars!
And then a big, a big rainbow right here! Big, very big rainbow! And so many clouds because... um...
And then a big, a big rainbow right here! A big, very big rainbow! And so many clouds because... um...
I don't know, I think it's just very aesthetic. Yeah, and the floor!
Floor... floor mite... wah! Nanka pattern, umi mitai. You know? Yeah, like my hair.
The floor... look at the floor... Whoa! It's like a pattern of the sea, you know? Yeah, like my hair.
So, um... don't forget to take a lot of screenshots, okay? Especially later, okay? Get a lot of screenshots!
Okay? And then post your comments, your moments, your impressions, your everything with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 on your SNS!
Sostara, kobo no 3D basude haishin SNS ni hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 wo tsukete comment ya omoide, kansou, nado nado to koshite ne! And...
So then, post your comments, memories, impressions, and everything on SNS with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 for Kobo's 3D birthday stream, okay? And...
Are you guys ready for the next performance? Mmm mmm mmm! Okay, let's go to the next performance...
Are you guys ready for the next performance? Mm-hm! Okay, let's go to the next performance...
at my last position
あ、オッケー！覚えています
Ah, okay! I remember.
それでは皆さん、準備いいか？Let's go to the next song!
Are you guys ready? Let's go to the next song!
とくべチュ、してじゃ足りない
Just a special chu isn't enough,
一番大事がいい
I want to be your absolute number one.
君がつくるオリジナルの とくべチュ、して
Give me your very own original special chu.
眩しくって目が覚めて
Blinded, my eyes snap open,
愛しくって想ってよ
Thinking of you so lovingly.
眠り姫のように 優しく口づけして
Like a sleeping princess, gently kiss me.
鳴り響いたこの世界
This world that resonates,
誘い掛かる君がいる
You are there, calling out to me.
全てに触れずに 二人だけでいよう
Without touching everything, let's be just the two of us.
私のこと独占して 君だけのものになってもいい
Monopolize me, it's okay if I become only yours.
なんでもない日の なんでもない気付いてね
On a completely ordinary day, notice the little things.
気づいてね
Please notice.
おーべびーあいらぶゆーじゃ足りない
Oh baby, I love you isn't enough,
君の特別にして
Make me your special one.
根元君にキスもう私は
Even more, give me a kiss, I...
君でいっぱいよ
...am full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
An untieable ribbon knot.
とくべチュって縛って
Tie me up with a special chu,
そうよ一緒、一緒がいいの
That's right, being together, being together is best.
特別が欲しい
I want something special.
二人きり週末は 奏でてよハーモニー
On just the two of us weekends, play our harmony.
出会え星見たら
If you see the meeting stars,
私を思ってほしい
I want you to think of me.
甘々な君なのに
Even though you're so sweet,
拾い街吸い込まれ
Drawn into the wide town.
戦う姿に 大きな花丸だね
Your fighting figure deserves a big gold star.
好きなところ 優しいとこ
The places I love: your kindness,
嫌いなとこも優しいとこ
Even the parts I dislike, because they're kind.
誰にもあげない
I won't give you to anyone.
私だけ独りじめしてね
Keep me all to yourself.
お前だって今までの人と 同じはいらないんだす
Even you don't need anyone like your past lovers.
根元君も私のため 生きてほしいんです
I want you to live for my sake too.
だから兎牙と私たちは絶対に離させないで
So don't ever let us apart.
そんなんじゃ束縛じゃないわ
That's not even bondage.
苦しいのが好き
I like it when it hurts.
ショートケーキ好き 一期みたいに座ってもいい
I can even sit like a shortcake favorite strawberry.
赤く甘い恋だもん
Because it's a red, sweet love.
誰が一番よ 大好きも
Who is the number one? Even my deep love,
返してもらって全部はなしに
Return it all to me and let go of everything.
頂戴もっと
Give me more!
君は神様が作る奇跡のような人 連れてきた顔もその笑顔も
You are like a miracle created by God, bringing that face and smile.
守ってあげるね
I will protect you.
おーべびーあいらぶゆーじゃ足りない
Oh baby, I love you isn't enough,
君の特別にして
Make me your special one.
根元君にキスもう私は
Even more, give me a kiss, I...
君でいっぱいよ
...am full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
An untieable ribbon knot.
とくべチュって縛って
Tie me up with a special chu,
ねぇベビ最初で最後の
Hey baby, for our first and last...
特別にしてね
...make it special.
ここここここここオープンセサミ
Koko koko koko koko open sesame!
闇と光の交わるパラダイスコード
The paradise code where darkness and light intersect.
今宵味わう快楽ケリコ
Tonight we taste pleasure, tell it.
踊り絡み合うゾディアック
The zodiac dancing and entangling.
恋の駆け引きのタイムブレイク
The time break of love's game.
叶わない存在 ただ強を引きたい
An unattainable existence, I just want to draw out your strength.
夢見心地ふれあい惑わせたい
In a dreamlike state, I want to touch and bewilder you.
曖昧解けないここって
Ambiguous, unwinnable, right here.
恋は甘い
Love is sweet,
朝焼けた赤い愛
red love in the morning glow,
見つめて限界
gazing until the limit.
月夜に誘われ
Lured by the moonlit night,
天使と
with an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon,
天使と
with an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon.
天使が悪魔を甘く過激した
The angel sweetly provoked the demon.
天国 地獄の
Between heaven and hell,
between heaven and hell,
天国 地獄の
天国 地獄の狭間で出会った
we met in the liminal space.
天使と
With an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon,
天使と
with an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon.
天使が悪魔が揃って踊れば
If angel and demon dance together,
天国
heaven
地獄の
and hell's
天国
heaven
地獄の門が開く
gates of hell will open.
涙と光の交わるファナティック
A fanaticism where tears and light intersect,
今宵味覚はサイケデリック
tonight's taste is psychedelic.
踊り絡み合うゾディアック
A zodiac dancing and intertwining,
恋の駆け引きのダイブレイク
a dive break of romantic bargaining.
Dead alive
Dead or alive,
dead or alive.
Dead dead dead ba-ba-ba dead dead dead
Dead alive
Dead or alive,
dead or alive.
Dead dead dead ba-ba-ba dead dead dead
Let's go!
生きた魂をトレイに置いて
Placing living souls upon the tray,
巡る五枚のカード揺れる炎
five spinning cards and swaying flames.
先にあなたがレイスしたら
If you make your raise first,
もう迷わないプラスの飲みほして
I won't hesitate anymore, drain the plus.
今夜おのろい織り成すこの勝負
This match woven with tonight's curse.
今 天国と地獄をつなぐ門が開いて
Now, the gates connecting heaven and hell open,
天使と悪魔 聖者と罪人が入り乱れ
angels and demons, saints and sinners mingle,
踊り 笑い 全ては混沌の中に飲み込まれていく
dancing and laughing as all is swallowed by chaos.
それは世界の終焉であり 新たなる始まりでもあるのだった
It was both the end of the world and a new beginning.
Dead alive
Dead or alive,
dead or alive.
Dead dead dead ba-ba-ba dead dead dead
Dead alive
Dead or alive,
dead or alive.
Dead dead dead ba-ba-ba dead dead dead
天国 地獄 天国 地獄
Heaven, hell, heaven, hell,
heaven, hell, heaven, hell.
天国 地獄 天国 地獄
Heaven, hell, heaven, hell,
heaven, hell, heaven, hell.
月夜に誘われ
Lured by the moonlit night,
天使と
with an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon,
天使と
with an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon.
天使が悪魔を甘く過激した
The angel sweetly provoked the demon.
天国 地獄の 核心消えない果てない悶々
The heart of heaven and hell, endless agony.
天国 地獄の 天国 地獄の 狭間で出会った
We met in the liminal space between heaven and hell.
天使と
With an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon,
天使と
with an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon.
天使と悪魔が揃って踊れば
If angel and demon dance together,
天国 地獄の 天国 地獄の 狭間で出会った
we met in the space between heaven and hell.
天使と
With an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon,
天使と
with an angel,
悪魔と
with a demon.
天使と悪魔が揃って踊れば
If angel and demon dance together,
Dead alive
dead or alive.
Dead or alive,
Dead dead dead ba-ba-ba dead dead dead
Dead alive
Dead or alive,
dead or alive.
Dead dead dead ba-ba-ba dead dead dead
天国 地獄 ゴー！
Heaven, hell, let's go!
Iblis darimana, kah?
Which demon are you?
Wah, Gatot Eror lagi. Iblis wauw-wauw waha-i!
Wow, Gatot Eror again. Wow-wow demon waha-i!
Itu, 4 tanduk, bahaya sebaloh sekali.
That's 4 horns, super dangerous!
Iya, jadi gini.
Yeah, so it's like this.
Aku datang jauh-jauh...
I came all this way...
Ya, jauh-jauh.
Yeah, all the way.
Apa? Meskipun tidak diundang?
What? Even though you weren't invited?
Ah, diundang!
Ah, I was invited!
Iya, kayaknya kamu ngundang yang lain itu tadi.
Yeah, feels like you invited someone else just now.
Maksudnya? Nyo Yimi?
What do you mean? Nyo Yimi?
Kenapa tiba-tiba nyungsep?
Why did you suddenly face-plant?
Kamu malaikat Jepang, ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa berhenti muter, enggak? Pusing. Pusing, ya udah.
Can you stop spinning? I'm dizzy. Dizzy, oh well.
Duh, malaikat kok pusing, guys.
Jeez, an angel getting dizzy, guys.
Iya, aku di sini soalnya datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya, pengen main bareng, pengen godain kamu aja.
Yeah, I'm actually just here to seduce you, play together, and tease you.
Sini, sini, sini, sini!
Come here, come here, come here!
Pulang, kamu habis ini. Loh, kamu habis ini pulang sama aku, kan?
You're going home. Hey, you're going home with me after this, right?
Pulang.
Home.
Iya. Habis ini enggak ada apa-apa lagi, kan?
Yeah. There's nothing else after this, right?
Ngapain? Enak-enak aku di atas.
Why? I'm having a great time up here.
Masa kamu seret aku?
Did you just drag me?
Loh, kita, loh, bukannya kita Kita, kita, loh, aja, iblis!
Hey, us, hey, aren't we... Us, us, just us, demon!
Ajak dong, ajak dong banget kamu. Saya ajak. Aku kesepian. Ayo, sini.
Invite me, invite me so much. I invited you. I'm lonely. Come here.
Barangnya Fallen Angel nih.
This is Fallen Angel stuff.
Enggak, enggak ada Fallen Angel, enggak ada, enggak ada Fallen Angel ya, guys.
No, there's no Fallen Angel, none at all, guys.
Sickness-nya aku panah. Iya, iya. Coba, coba, coba, coba!
I'll shoot your sickness. Yeah, yeah. Try it, try it!
Satu, dua, tiga!
One, two, three!
Waa!
How to tame your demon? How to tame your demon?
Jadi Light Novel.
Becoming a light novel.
Eh, gimana tadi freestyle kita keren banget ya, guys?
Hey, how was our freestyle just now? It was super cool, right guys?
Iya, lucu gak sih?
Yeah, super cute, right?
Atas, bawah, atas, bawah, atas, bawah...
Up, down, up, down, up, down...
Terus, tapi pas kamu atas, aku bawah. Kebalik.
And then, but when you went up, I went down. It was reversed.
Tau ya, orang mah kebalik kiri kanan. Dia bilang cetak atas.
I know, right? Normal people go left and right. She said 'print up'.
Atas. Aku bawah. Atas.
Up. I'm down. Up.
Kocak-kocak. Ya udah, ya udah.
So funny. Oh well, whatever.
Ya udah, kalau gitu aku mau...
Well, if that's the case, I want to...
aku wanita sibuk ya sebenarnya.
I'm actually a busy woman, you know.
Jadi kayak, emang enggak ada waktu, aku di sini mampir.
So like, I don't really have time, I'm just dropping by here.
Kasih 5 detik buat kamu. Bumi pinjam Goku nih.
Giving you 5 seconds. Goku's borrowing Earth here.
Asyik! Oke! Baik!
Awesome! Okay! Sounds good!
Fiksi ya, guys. Ini cerita fiksi. Jangan ditiru.
It's fiction, guys. This is a fictional story. Don't copy it.
Sensitif ini, sensitif. Fiksi, boongan.
It's sensitive, sensitive. Fiction, fake.
Oke, kalau gitu, bye!
Okay, if that's it, bye!
Enggak mau ikut aku lagi... Jagain nih anak ya, guys.
I don't want to come with you anymore... Take care of this kid, guys.
Bisa jadi Fallen Angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I might become a Fallen Angel because of her instigation, guys.
Enggak jelas.
Makes no sense.
ときめきキュン！で大暴走♡
Pounding kyun! Going wild♡
なんとかしなくちゃじゃなくて 突然メイドになっちゃって
It's not that I have to, I suddenly became a maid
いつものように お店の掃除 扉 開いちゃって目が合った
Cleaning the shop like always, opening the door and our eyes met
なんだか忙しくなっちゃって あわてんぼうにもなっちゃって
Somehow I got so busy, and became such a scatterbrain
お仕事中に おしに夢中に どこを探しても見つからないじゃん
Busy at work, obsessed with my crush, I can't find them anywhere
もう一回 ちょっと待って
One more time, wait a second
もういいよ 秘密だよね？
That's enough. It's a secret, right?
もういいの 好きになっちゃって ねぇ
Is that enough? I've fallen in love, hey...
好きって言って？
Will you say you love me?
ドキドキキュン 送るラブビーム 君を夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
Pounding kyun, sending a love beam, a magic making you obsessed
ほら ドキドキキュン 私だいぼうそう 君を夢中にさせる恋の味
Look, pounding kyun, I'm going wild, the taste of love making you obsessed
もう君にキュン 私だいぼうそう 君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
Already kyun for you, I'm going wild, a magic letting us get obsessed
だから君がキュンってなる恋になって 一つどうぞこれが恋の味
So you fall into a kyun-inducing love, here's a taste of love
楽しくて仕方なくたって そそろ終わりになっちゃって
Even if it's too fun, it's almost coming to an end
会いたくなって 落ち込んじゃって 君とぶつかって目が合った
Wanting to see you, feeling down, I bumped into you and our eyes met
何度も会いたくなって 今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
Wanting to meet again and again, today alone isn't enough
計画通り 私の勝利 君に会いたくて仕方がないよ
According to plan, my victory! I can't help wanting to see you
もう一回 ちょっと待って
One more time, wait a second
もういいよ 君だけだよ
That's enough. It's only you.
もうずっとな愛し合いたいよ ねぇ
I want us to love each other forever, hey...
好きって言って？
Will you say you love me?
ドキドキキュン 君にラブビーム 二人夢中になれる魔法じゃん
Pounding kyun, a love beam to you, a magic for us to get lost in
ほら ドキドキキュン 私だいれいあい 君を夢中にさせる恋の魔法
Look, pounding kyun, my great love, the magic of love making you obsessed
もう君にキュン 私だいこうらん 君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
Already kyun for you, my great confusion, a magic letting us get obsessed
だから君がキュンってなる恋になって 一つどうぞこれが恋の味
So you fall into a kyun-inducing love, here's a taste of love
パワー このままだったら ここで会うこともなくなって
Power... If it stays like this, we won't even meet here anymore
もう君の声が聞きたくなるの
And I'll want to hear your voice even more
もう一回 ちょっと待って
One more time, wait a second
もういいの 秘密なのに
That's enough, even though it's a secret
もういいよ このまま好きになってく
That's enough, I'll keep falling in love just like this
好きって言って？
Will you say you love me?
ドキドキキュン 送るラブビーム 君を夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
Pounding kyun, sending a love beam, a magic making you obsessed
ほら ドキドキキュン 私だいぼうそう 君を夢中にさせる恋の味
Look, pounding kyun, I'm going wild, the taste of love making you obsessed
もう君にキュン 私だいぼうそう 君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
Already kyun for you, I'm going wild, a magic letting us get obsessed
だから君がキュンってなる恋になって 一つどうぞこれが恋の味
So you fall into a kyun-inducing love, here's a taste of love
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Wangi tuh udah mulai gelap tapi, masih pada semangat enggak semuanya?
Even though it's starting to get dark, are you guys still energetic?
あ、たくさんのゲストとパフォーマンスをしてから、
Ah, after performing with so many guests,
次は、コボはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います。
I think Kobo wants to sing alone again next.
これから歌うこの曲は、最近コボが気に入っている曲で、聴いたら幸せな気持ちになりました。
The song I'll sing next is one I've been loving recently, and listening to it makes me feel so happy.
皆さんも、この曲聴いて幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be so happy if you all listen to this song and feel that happiness too.
それでは、次の曲、青木テルマさんの「Happiness」です！
And now, for the next song, Aoyama Teruma's "Happiness"!
Oh wherever you are
何も言わなくても
Even without saying anything,
感じているよの One for me
I feel it, you're the one for me.
You always make me happy
抱き込んで 眠れなくて
Holding you, unable to sleep,
キミとの写真 見つめている
Staring at photos of you and me.
いくつもの 笑顔たちに 助けられるよ My life
Saved by so many smiles, oh my life.
ずっと一緒だよ 泣いてもいいよ
We'll always be together, it's okay to cry.
あの涙を 抱きしめてくれた ドコにいるの ココにいるから
Embracing those tears, wherever you are, I'm right here.
すぐに会いたいって キミと Happiness
Wanting to meet you right away, Happiness with you...
キミがいれば 大丈夫だって思えるよ
As long as you're here, I know I'll be okay.
何も言わなくても 感じているよの One for me
Even without saying anything, I feel it, you're the one for me.
キミと Happiness どんな時も 一人じゃないって信じてるよ
Happiness with you, believing I'm never alone no matter what.
涙 あふれたって 歩けるね Please stay by my side
Even when tears overflow, I can walk on, please stay by my side.
キミに出会えてからは 素直に笑っていられるよ
Ever since I met you, I can smile honestly.
少しずつ 自分のこと 好きになった For you...
Little by little, I grew to love myself, for you...
そう今なら ねぇ 心から 分かり合えると 思えるよ
Yes, now I feel we can truly understand each other from the heart.
強がらずに ありのままでも 見つめてくれた
You looked at me just as I was, without having to act strong.
だから Happiness キミのことを 今よりももっと知りたいって
That's why, Happiness, I want to know even more about you than now.
どんな言葉よりも 大切なよの One for me
More than any words, you're the precious one for me.
私もキミに 何かできることしたいよ いつでも一緒だから
I want to do something for you too, because we're always together.
守ってゆけるから ずっと...
Because I can protect you, always...
キミと Happiness キミがいれば 大丈夫だって思えるよ
Happiness with you, as long as you're here, I know I'll be okay.
何も言わなくても 感じているよの One for me
Even without saying anything, I feel it, you're the one for me.
キミと Happiness どんな時も 一人じゃないって信じてるよ
Happiness with you, believing I'm never alone no matter what.
涙 あふれたって 歩けるね Please stay by my side
Even when tears overflow, I can walk on, please stay by my side.
大切なよの One for me
You're the precious one for me.
You always make me happy
Smile for me, baby
ようこそお越しなさったご主人様
Welcome, esteemed master who has come to visit,
隣に座らせーの 萌え萌え萌え萌え
Sit down next to me, moe moe moe moe!
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who could possibly be happy with this?
ねぇ教えて笑顔で up, pull, pull
Hey, tell me with a smile: up, pull, pull!
愛想を忘れてご苦労様 私とあなたでせーの love, love, love, love
Good job forgetting your friendliness—ready, set: love, love, love, love!
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who could possibly be happy with this?
ねぇ教えて笑顔で up, pull, pull
Hey, tell me with a smile: up, pull, pull!
ひらり はらり 女の子
Fluttering, drifting girls,
ふわり ふわり 言葉のソー
Floating, drifting words,
それって つまり お冷な娘
That means you're a cold-hearted girl,
感情的 リアル 笑顔で up, pull, pull
Emotional and real, smiling with up, pull, pull!
人は 見かけ によらぬもの
You can't judge a book by its cover,
嘘を嘘だと見抜けない
Can't even tell lies from truth,
したたかな袖裾の革
Stubborn leather on the sleeves and hem,
鳥肌気味肌 アンドゥトロワ
Goosebumps on my skin, un, deux, trois!
間違ったご指名を頂きます
Thank you for the wrong nomination!
私とあなたでせーの love, love, love, love
You and me together, ready: love, love, love, love!
これはど派手にご苦労様
Good job being so flashy,
遊びましょう笑顔で up, brrt, brrt
Let's play with a smile: up, brrt, brrt!
ひらり はらり ここは何処
Fluttering, drifting, where is this?
ふわり ふわり 掃討 let me show
Floating, drifting, sweeping—let me show!
それって つまり お冷な娘
That means you're a cold-hearted girl,
確証的なリアル 笑顔で up, brrt, brrt
Definitive and real, smiling with up, brrt, brrt!
歌い出す秘密の鐘
The secret bell starts to ring,
終わることのないこの世界
In this endless world,
悲しい子供は 虚しい子供は
Sad children, empty children,
眠らせて
Let them sleep.
おままごと遊びましょう笑顔で up, pull, pull
Let's play house with a smile: up, pull, pull!
ひらり はらり 女の子
Fluttering, drifting girls,
ふわり ふわり 言葉のソー
Floating, drifting words,
それって つまり お冷な娘
That means you're a cold-hearted girl,
感情的 リアル 笑顔で up, pull, pull
Emotional and real, smiling with up, pull, pull!
遊びましょう笑顔で up, pull, pull
Let's play with a smile: up, pull, pull!
up, pull, pull
ひらりはらり 女の子
Fluttering, drifting girls,
ふわりふわり 言葉のソー
Floating, drifting words,
それってつまり お冷な娘
That means you're a cold-hearted girl,
感情的リアル 笑顔で up, pull, pull
Emotional and real, smiling with up, pull, pull!
遊びましょう笑顔で up, pull, pull
Let's play with a smile: up, pull, pull!
up, pull, pull
Let's dance with me! SUNDAY NIGHT MAGIC
何回でもできるマジック
A magic trick we can do anytime,
まだまだ今日は夢心地
Today still feels like a dream.
曜日のことでも忘れたって
Even if we forget what day it is,
何処でも行けた まさか
We could go anywhere—wait, really?
明日が来るその日まで
Until the day tomorrow comes,
ねぇ ぼくどうだい
Hey, how about me?
ふさぎ込んでる週の終わりに
At the end of a gloomy week,
退屈そうだけどどうだろう
You look bored, but what do you think?
誘っていいかな
Can I invite you out?
噛まない 噛まない かもわかんない
I might not stumble my words,
こっち向いてる あっち向いてる
Looking this way, looking that way,
あっち向いてわ なんかじゃなくて
Instead of looking away somewhere,
キミのことだもん
It's all about you!
もっとちゃんとはなし聞いてよ
So listen to me properly!
Hey, let's seeから逆転
Hey, turning the tables from 'Let's see',
昨日の夜よりもの方がかわいいし
It's cuter than last night's evening,
言っても立ってもいられないし
I just can't sit still anymore!
聞こえる？動き出すチャイム
Can you hear the chiming bell starting up?
時間切れのその先へ
Beyond the time limit,
飛び出して 駆け出して
Leaping out, running fast,
まだまだ夜は終われない
The night still can't end!
こんな最高の日々が
If these amazing days
明日も続いてくなら
Will continue tomorrow too,
ねぇ キミもどうだい
Hey, how about you too?
待ち望んでるキミの理想の
Let's make sure your longed-for ideal
お姫様の席をどしっとしよう 狙っていいかな
Princess seat is secure—can I aim for it?
ネクチャン スラッジャス エイ 今じゃない？
Neck-chan, sludge-us, hey, isn't now the time?
ネコマタシャクシも局に合わせて
Everyone matching the tune,
ステップなんか踏んでみてご機嫌そう
Stepping along and looking so cheerful!
昨日の夜よりもっと楽しくて
Even more fun than last night,
続けたい時には
When you want it to keep going,
聞こえる？動き出すチャイム
Can you hear the chiming bell starting up?
時間切れのその先へ
Beyond the time limit,
終わらない 止まらない
Never ending, never stopping,
まだまだ夜長いから
Because the night is still long!
こんな 最高の日が
Such a wonderful day...
体を預けてみたら
If you try putting your body into it,
ほら、魔法みたい
See? It's like magic.
騒がしくてバカらしいようなって無茶苦茶な毎日がいい
Living so frantically that I wonder how such nonsense is even possible,
魔法なんてありえないでもここニャだけは現実になるかも
Well, that's impossible, but maybe it could be real here.
まわるよ夜を揺らして踊りにのぼて踊れ君を
Dancing in the night, dancing on steps, dancing with you.
そんな夜に飛びきりの魔法を
I'll cast a sudden spell on you tonight as well.
君にもかけたいから僕の手を取ってよ
I'll reach out to you too, so take my hand.
聞かせるなりやまないミュージック魔法が解けるまで最高で
A ringing bell, unstoppable music, the magic is born until the very end,
最強な夜が今日も更けていく
and even tonight, the strongest night goes on.
こんな夢みたいな日々が明日も続いてくならね君は断らない
If tomorrow continues like this dream-like day, hey, don't you agree?
あくほど大胆に夜を飾るストーリー何回でもかける中マジ
Spinning a legend into the bold night, casting a spell time and time again,
まだまだ続くよ夢心地
still, still, it's a dream-like comfort.
嘘みたいだけど朝が来るその時までね僕とドライ
It sounds like a lie, but until that dawn breaks, hey, take my hand.
うぇー！
Woo!
ここどこ？
Hey, where are we?
わけんニャ？
Wait, what?
なんか雲美味しそうじゃん！
Doesn't that cloud look delicious?
食べてみんないや！
Eat it, everyone!
おいしい！
Delicious!
ちょっと待って、シャッセって何？シャッセ。
Wait, what is "chasse"?
何してるの？
What are you doing?
シャッセ、シャッセ！
Chasse, chasse!
最初はシャッセです。
First is chasse.
待って、見守ってた見守ってた。
Wait, I'm watching over you.
最初は食べてないです。
Wait, I haven't eaten it yet.
誰が？
Who is that?
ちょっと、シャッセ、シャッセ、そして…
Wait, chasse, chasse, and...
ちゃちゃモニャ！
Chachamonya!
ちゃちゃじゃ…ちゃちゃもにゃ！
Chacha... wait, no!
何してるの？
What are you doing?
Today is your birthday!
お誕生日！
Happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ウェルカム、ウェルカム！
Welcome! Welcome!
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
えー、じゃあ
Now then,
コボ先輩と一緒に歌って踊りたい！
Kobo-senpai wants to sing and dance together!
歌って踊りたい！アルゼンチンきゃん。
We want to sing and dance together! Argentina, yeah!
オッケー、オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay, okay.
コボ、振り付け！
Kobo, furitsuke (choreography)!
コボの振り付け！
Kobo's furitsuke!
コボの、え、コボ先生と呼んでください。
Please call me Kobo-sensei!
がっきだ、がっき！
Gakki (instrument/senior)!
がっき！
Gakki!
じゃあ、勉強した？
Okay, did you study?
もちろん！
Of course!
コボージュ先輩じゅうこれ地理？
Kobo-senpai, senior-juu, is this geography?
いや、こうゆうご、地理。
No, this is go-ography (geography)!
地理な。
Geography, yeah.
じゃあ、行きますよ。
Well, let's go!
行きますよ。オッケー。レッツゴー！
Let's go! Okay.
おお、いいね！
Oh, nice!
星樹の木！
Hoshiju no ki (Tree of Hoshiju / Starry Tree)!
オッケー！星樹の木！
Okay! Hoshiju no ki!
オッケー、オッケー。じゃあ行きましょう。
Okay, okay. Let's go!
誰も居なくなった 二人だけの街に
In a town where no one else remains, just the two of us,
機械仕掛けの時計が 夜の訪れ知らせる
the clockwork mechanism announces the arrival of night.
夕闇が空を ワイン色に染めて
Dyeing the twilight sky wine-red,
不慣れな二人を 舞台へと誘う
it invites the unaccustomed pair onto the stage.
Chasse 'n' Whisk 'n' Natural-Turn
貴方に魔法をあげる
I'll give you magic,
Throwaway and Oversway
その名前は honey mead
its name is honey mead.
蜜月 Un・Deux・Trois 互いの指を絡めて
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois, entangling our fingers,
二人の夢を奏でる
playing our dreams.
Chasse 'n' Whisk 'n' Natural-Turn
貴女に魔法をかける
casting magic on you,
Throwaway and Oversway 魅惑の蜜 honey mead
Throwaway and Oversway, seductive nectar honey mead,
蜜月 Un・Deux・Trois その唇を重ねて
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois, overlapping our lips.
また振り出しで構わないさ honey
It's okay to start over from scratch, honey
気になってた大概も fade away
Most of what was bothering me fades away
君と行こう come what may
I'll go with you, come what may
二人でいつからか人並みに well done
Together, before we knew it, doing well like everyone else
思いやりのが狭間で恋は揺れて swingin'
Love sways in the narrow space of consideration, swingin'
Latu-ya, latu-ya, Latu-ya, latu-ya, yeah
愛も言いなりじゃ足りそうもないさ darling
Love isn't enough just by being obedient, darling
朝焼けに染まるわ
It gets dyed in the morning glow
案外無邪気に笑ってるくらいが real
Smiling quite innocently is real
君と let's start this day
Let's start this day with you
幸い何気に手が触れるくらいで..
Fortunately, just touching hands casually...
You and I Do you remember? Hope you remember
刹那の feeling 朝焼けの orange sky
The feeling of a fleeting moment, the orange morning sky
Do you remember? Hope you remember
二人で見た view 黄昏の sunset clouds
The view we saw together, the twilight sunset clouds
Do you remember? Hope you remember
めくるめく淡い夢よ Every little thing's gonna be alright
A dizzying, fleeting dream, every little thing's gonna be alright
倦怠やら馴染み合いは移り行く時の phase
Boredom and familiarity are phases of changing times
語る夢も思い出も溶け合うわ face to face
The dreams and memories we talk about melt together face to face
おざなりなふりでの強がりな light な kiss
A show of indifference, a strong, light kiss
前よりで気分次第やり過ごすわ swingin'
Moving forward, passing the time on a whim, swingin'
Latu-ya, latu-ya, Latu-ya, latu-ya, yeah
愛の行方なら見えそうもないさ darling
The whereabouts of love don't seem visible, darling
But, 君となら行けるさ
But I can go if it's with you
大抵少しの思い揺れるくらいで tears
Mostly with just a slight shaking of emotion, tears
君と let's start this day
Let's start this day with you
幸い二人と同じ空見たいなら..
Fortunately, if we want to see the same sky together...
You and I Do you remember? Hope you remember
刹那の feeling 身を寄せた starry night
The feeling of a fleeting moment, a starry night where we drew close
Do you remember? Hope you remember
寂しげな moon light 掠れゆく shooting star
A lonely moonlight, a fading shooting star
Do you remember? Hope you remember
めくるめく淡い夢よ Every little thing's gonna be alright
A dizzying, fleeting dream, every little thing's gonna be alright
案外無邪気に笑ってるくらいが real
Smiling quite innocently is real
Let's recall it again
幸い二人と同じ明日に描くなら..
Fortunately, if we draw the same tomorrow together...
Baby, You and I Do you remember? Hope you remember
刹那の feeling 朝焼けの orange sky
The feeling of a fleeting moment, the orange morning sky
Do you remember? Hope you remember
二人で見た view 黄昏の sunset clouds
The view we saw together, the twilight sunset clouds
Do you remember? Hope you remember
刹那の feeling 身を寄せた starry night
The feeling of a fleeting moment, a starry night where we drew close
Do you remember? Hope you remember
めくるめく淡い夢よ Every little thing's gonna be alright
A dizzying, fleeting dream, every little thing's gonna be alright
Everything's gonna be alright
楽しかった！
That was fun!
楽しかったね！
It was fun, right!
やったー！
Yay!
ダンス上手！ダンス上手！
Good at dancing! Good at dancing!
ニューヨーク、スワン、こぼ先輩もしゅわん！
New York, Swan, Kobo-senpai is also shwan!
スワン、必ずスワン！
Swan, definitely swan!
スワン、スワン、スワン！
Swan, swan, swan!
ビューティフルスワン！
Beautiful swan!
ビューティフルスワン、めっちゃエレガント！
Beautiful swan, super elegant!
え、これ踊るの難しかった！
Eh, dancing this was hard!
あ、りじょ
Ah, little by little...
Do it, do it, えい、や、や！
Do it, do it, ei, ya, ya!
簡単です、簡単だよ！
It's easy, it's easy!
楽しかった！楽しかった！
That was fun! That was fun!
呼んでくれてありがとうね、こぼ先輩！
Thanks for inviting me, Kobo-senpai!
ありがとう、ぼくぼく！
Thank you, Boku-boku!
一緒に踊ってくれてもありがとう！
Thank you for dancing with us too!
またね、またね！
See you later, see you later!
またね、またね！ほんまに！またね！
See you later! Really! See you later!
ハッピーバースデー！
Happy Birthday!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ハッピーバースデー！ファイト！ファイト！
Happy Birthday! Fight! Fight!
じゃ、バイバーイ！
Well then, bye-bye!
みんな帰っちゃった。
Everyone went home.
寂しい。楽しい。誰も来ないのかな。
Lonely. Fun. I wonder if no one else is coming.
さようならの前に キスをして
Before saying goodbye, give me a kiss
さようならのあとは 忘れさせて
After saying goodbye, make me forget
でも あなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't disappear
離れない 話せない 戻りたい
Can't stay away, can't speak, I want to go back
Take me free
この歌は君が言った
This song is what you said...
あなたみたいになりたかった
I wanted to be like you,
ひとりごとを呟いた
I mumbled to myself.
知らないうちに冷めてしまった紅茶とクッキー
Before I knew it, my tea and cookies had gone cold.
扉の外で声がして
I heard a voice behind the door.
いつしか理由も忘れて
Before I knew it, I'd forgotten the reason,
届かないその言葉に首を締め付けられているのになぜ
Choking on those words that wouldn't reach you.
なぜ
Why?
回答なんて持ってないよそんなの
An answer? I don't have such a thing.
だいたい正解なんてつまんないってそうでしょう?
The correct answer is boring anyway, isn't that right?
気まぐれの一歩 それって気のせい?
It's caprice—in other words, it's all in my head.
黙ってりゃ犠牲になってくだけ
If you stay silent, you'll only be sacrificed.
うらうら続く日々に綻び
A tear in the sluggishly passing days.
CLOSET
始まらない
It won't begin.
なにも知らない
I don't know anything.
もうひとつも愛さない
I will never love another one again.
CLOSET
間違い無い
Without a mistake...
どうにもできない 痛みのその先を
In no way can I stand what comes after pain.
あなたみたいになりたかった
I wanted to be like you,
ひとりごとを呟いた
I mumbled to myself.
知らないうちに飽きてしまった後悔も全部
Before I knew it, I got fed up with my regrets.
扉の外で声がして
I heard a voice behind the door.
いつしか理由も忘れて
Before I knew it, I'd forgotten the reason.
助けないその言葉に決めつけられて生きているのになぜ
Those helpless words determined my life.
なぜ
Why?
何回だって待ってたんだ知ってる
Countless times I waited, I'm aware.
生存本能だって「解ってる」をやっている
It's a survival instinct to always say "I know".
噛らってっ罵声 奪ってっ個性
The feasting boos, the tendency to take,
腐ってる和製の番狂わせ
The rotten Japanese-made upset.
のらりくらり続く日々の移ろい
A change in the aimlessly passing days.
CLOSET
始まらない
It won't begin.
なにもできない
I can't do anything.
もうひとつも返せない
I will never return a single one again.
CLOSET
間違い無い
Without a mistake...
なんてくらない 痛みのその先へ
Beyond such absurd pain.
小さなこの部屋の扉を叩いている
I knock on the door of this small room,
知らない街へ連れ出していく
Taking you out to an unfamiliar town.
震える手を前に差し出している あなたに触れるまで
Holding out my shaking hand until I feel you.
CLOSET
「さよなら」という言葉は短いけれど
"Saying goodbye" is short,
そこに込められた想いは永遠に等しい
Yet the feelings poured into it feel eternal.
あなたの姿探した 夕暮れのあとりうむ
I searched for your figure in the twilight atrium.
心の内灯した ほんとの小さな光を今も忘れないよ
I still haven't forgotten that tiny light lit deep in my heart.
二人が出会ったその理由は 傷つけ合うためじゃなく
The reason we met was not to hurt each other,
お互いに足りない何かを分け合うためだった
But to share what each of us lacked.
ずっと逢いたくて ただ逢いたくて
I always wanted to see you, just wanted to see you.
涙がこぼれる日も
Even on days when tears spill over,
今は思い出を胸に抱いて 歩いて行こう
Let's walk on, keeping those memories in our hearts.
人はそう段々に 愛を失い
Do people gradually lose love,
そして人を愛することに目覚めていくのかな?
And then awaken to loving someone?
何もかもなくして 振り返ったその時
When we lose everything and look back,
燃え尽きた心にある一つの想い信じてみよう もう一度
Let's believe in the single feeling left in our burnt-out hearts once more.
二人が見た夢はまだ 言葉には出来ないけれど
The dream we shared cannot yet be put into words,
思い出に変わるまでは そう 失さないでいて
So until it turns into a memory, please don't lose it.
いつも大好きで ただ大好きで
I always loved you, just loved you.
一人ぼっちの夜も あなたは言ってくれた
Even on lonely nights, you told me,
「自分らしく生きればいい」と
"You just need to live as yourself."
あなたと見つけた眩しい時間は もう二度と帰らないから
The dazzling time we found together will never return,
感じられたことのすべてを 忘れないでいて
So please don't forget everything we were able to feel.
ずっと逢いたくて ただ逢いたくて
I always wanted to see you, just wanted to see you.
涙がこぼれる日も
Even on days when tears spill over,
今は思い出を胸に抱いて 歩いて行こう
Let's walk on, keeping those memories in our hearts.
待ち合わせの5分前 から
5 minutes before our meeting,
早く 会いたくて そわそわ し てる
I've been so anxious, wanting to see you soon.
昨日 も 一緒 に 居た の に ね
Even though we were together just yesterday,
時間 が 止まって も 全然 足りない
even if time stopped, it's not nearly enough.
手 を 繋ぐ 距離 が 好き すぎ て
I love the distance when we hold hands so much,
離れ ない よう に ぎゅっ て する の
squeezing tight so we won't drift apart.
お泊まり の あれこれ だって
All those little sleepover things—
あなた なら 全部 あげ ちゃう から
I'd give them all to you, because it's you.
抱きしめて よ そば に いて
Hold me close, stay by my side,
世界 が ふわっ と 明るく なる の
and the world grows softly, brightly lit.
これ が 恋 だ と 知った 日 から
From the day I learned this feeling was love,
今日 も あなた で 溢れて いく ん だ
today too, I'm overflowing with thoughts of you.
ねぇ 、 抑え切れ ない 想い
Hey, these feelings I can't hold back—
あなた が 居ない と ダメ みたい で
it's like I'm no good without you around.
こんな 気持ち 知ら なかっ た よ
I never knew a feeling quite like this,
初めて 恋 に 夢中 に なった の
losing myself in love for the very first time.
身長 は 理想 より 低い けど
Though you're a bit shorter than my ideal,
顔 だって ド タイプ って わけ で も ない し
and you're not exactly my usual type either,
どこ に 惚れ た ん だろ 。 って
wondering just where I fell for you,
ほら 気付け ば あなた の こと ばかり で
before I knew it, I was only thinking of you.
些細な こと に も 付き合って
You indulge me in the littlest things,
私 の こと 理解 し て くれる
and you truly understand who I am.
人生 に 悩んだ 時 も
Even when I'm troubled by life,
大丈夫 って 包み込ん で くれる の
you wrap me in your arms and say it'll be okay.
抱きしめて よ そば に いて
Hold me close, stay by my side,
どんな 景色 も 分け合いたい から
because I want to share every scenery with you.
会え ない 夜 が 増える ほど に
The more nights we have to spend apart,
あなた を また 好き に なって くんだ
the more deeply I fall in love with you again.
ねぇ 、 迷惑 し て ない か な
Hey, am I bothering you at all?
笑わ れ ちゃう くらい あなた ばかり
It's laughable how it's all about you.
好き じゃ 足りない 愛 の 言葉
Saying 'I love you' isn't nearly enough words,
どうやって 伝え たら 届い て くれる の
how can I convey it so it reaches your heart?
口数 が 少なく なっ たり
Even if you grow a little quiet,
倦怠期 に 襲わ れ て も
or we get hit by a slump in our days,
私 が 繋ぎ 続ける から
I'll keep holding our hands together,
だって 仕方ない よ こんなに こんなに 好き だ から
because I can't help it, I love you so, so much.
抱きしめて よ あなた だけ
Hold me close, you and you alone,
まだ 知ら ない 未来 も 一緒 が いい
I want us together in futures we've yet to know.
くっつく たび 離れ られ ない
Every time we cuddle, we can never let go,
生まれ変わっ て も 見つける ん だ
and even if we're reborn, I'll find you again.
ねぇ 、 私 幸せ だ から さ
Hey, since I'm so happy right now,
これ 以上 何 も 望ま ない よ
I don't wish for anything more than this.
ただ 隣 で 笑って い て ね
Just keep smiling right by my side,
あなた の 恋 に 夢中 に なった の
I'm completely, hopelessly in love with you.
So... How is it guys?
ではclosing?
The closing...
Do you take a lot of screenshots? Ooh! And ah!
How about my new stage? Look!
It's very cloudy here. Yeah, as you can see,
there's two big chillis on the left and right. Hmm! So cute right?
みんなどうだった？Koboのパフォーマンス。いっぱいスクリーンショット取れたかな？
How was it, everyone? Kobo's performance. Were you able to take lots of screenshots?
Koboの新しいステージはもうどうだった？可愛いでしょう？
How was Kobo's new stage? Cute, right?
ビッグチリズがありますので、めっちゃ可愛いよね。
There are big chillies on it, so it's super cute, right?
うん、so actually, yeah we're already at the end of the show guys. But,
Yeah, so actually, yeah we're already at the end of the show guys. But,
そろそろ終わり時間になりますよ。
it's almost time to wrap things up.
But don't worry, hmm. Kobo still have something to share with you guys. まだ皆さんにお知らせがあります。
But don't worry, hmm. Kobo still has something to share with you guys. I have an announcement for everyone.
じゃーん！ジャーン！
Tada! Tada!
Birthday 2025! Kobo Kanaeru special birthday 2025 merch set! This time Kobo's birthday merch theme is jellyfish.
Princess,
I've wanted to wear a jellyfish costume
for a long time,
and finally my wish came true.
So, how is it, guys?
Do I look beautiful?
And the KV is drawn by Skotty-sensei.
Skotty-sensei, arigatou!
Arigatou! And as usual, guys,
Finally, ta-da!
Bokobokers, Happi is here!
Now you can proudly wear it
to cheer me on during events.
So cool! Happy, happy, happy!
Come on, buy happy, happy!
And if you look closely, this happi design
is like my raincoat, right?
You can see there's two 'i's in the front
and 'me' in the back, right? And...
Next, we have the
"Jellyfish Princess on the Wall" Tapestry.
It's printed with my brand new birthday illustration.
It's super high quality
and perfect for decorating your wall.
You can wake up and see Kobo's smug face every morning,
and also don't forget to praise the Lord every day.
Then look at this!
The "Jellyfish Princess, you got this!" Button Badge Set
One has my birthday outfit
and the other is an illustration I drew.
It looks good, right? Do you like it?
I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag
or your hat, or your hat, hehe.
Okay, so this one is one of my favorites.
One, two, three!
Ta-da! The plushie keychain!
It's me, but mini Kobo in mini form.
You can bring me anywhere—on your backpack,
keys, motorcycle, car, or next to your PC.
So soft and squeezable!
And finally,
we also have the situational voice pack.
So it's called "Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess".
What does it mean? Buy it! Buy it,
okey, so you know what it means.
It's a special voice pack where I talk to you
about the Jellyfish Princess just for you.
Yeah, don't miss out on my birthday merch, guys.
If you buy a set of them,
you'll get a special bromide with my signature on it.
Available for a limited time only,
grab yours from the official shop.
So, yeah, that's all for the announcement.
Thank you for coming and watching Kobo's performance today.
Ijō de oshirase deshita.
Links are in the description and chat.
That's all for the announcement.
Oya? But I can hear some of you
want an encore. You want an encore?
Oh? But I can hear some of you
なつかしい 痛みだわ
A familiar ache
A familiar ache...
ずっと前に 忘れていた
I forgot all about it a while ago,
でも あなたを 見たとき
but when I saw you,
時間だけ 後戻り したの
I went back in time for a moment.
「幸福？」と聞かないで
Don't ask me if I'm happy,
嘘つくのは 上手じゃない
I'm not good at lying.
友達なら いるけれど
I have friends,
あんなには 燃え上がれなくて
but I can't burn as brightly as I did then.
失った 夢だけが
Why is it only the dreams we've lost
美しく 見えるのは 何故かしら
that seem so beautiful?
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Now even your long-past kindness
甘い 記憶 sweet memories
is a sweet memory, sweet memories.
あの頃は 若すぎて
Back then, we were much too young,
過ちで 傷つけあった二人
and we hurt each other for no good reason.
色褪せた 哀しみも 今は
Now even my faded sadness
遠い 記憶 sweet memories
is a distant memory, sweet memories.
失った 夢だけが
Why is it only the dreams we've lost
美しく 見えるのは 何故かしら
that seem so beautiful?
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Now even your long-past kindness
甘い 記憶 sweet memories
is a sweet memory, sweet memories.
失った 夢だけが
Why is it only the dreams we've lost
美しく 見えるのは 何故かしら
that seem so beautiful?
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Now even your long-past kindness
甘い 記憶 sweet memories
is a sweet memory, sweet memories.
君はほんとにわかってないよ
You really don't understand it,
例えばハッピーエンドより
for example, rather than a happy ending...
君はほんとにわかってないよ
You really don't understand it.
思えば君の何気ない言葉が
Thinking back on it, those casual words of yours
この心支えて強さをくれたね
strengthened my heart and gave me strength.
失くしたモノに怯えていた僕を
The me who was frightened of what I'd lost,
確かな決意で導いてくれたんだよ
you guided me with certain determination.
二つの傘より
Rather than sharing two umbrellas,
あいあい傘さし ちょっと冷たいけど
sharing a lover's umbrella—even if it's a bit chilly,
愛するための
if it's for the sake of love,
代償ならいくらでもどうぞ
whatever the price, gladly.
ずっとそばにいたい ねぇ 誰と
I want to stay by your side forever—hey, with whom?
欲するもの何ひとつない
There's nothing else I desire,
ふたりぼっちの世界でずっと 最後の花火を上げて
in a world where it's just the two of us, forever launching our final fireworks,
フィナーレを飾って 奇跡の古巣 恋に落ちて
gracing our finale, falling in love within the nest of miracles—
誰も話さないで
no one, please don't let go,
味気ない世界も歩かないで
don't walk through this insipid world alone.
どんなに恋をしたって 出逢えないよきっと 終わりもない
No matter how much I fall in love, I'll surely never find an end—
幸せに気付こうよ
let's realize this happiness.
いつか 今日を 忘れても
Even if someday you forget today,
君がいるんだよ 天気雨の日
you are here with me, on a sunshower day.
出逢いとして始めて 目があったら ずっと 覚えとくよ
Starting as a chance meeting, the moment our eyes met—I'll remember it forever.
ねぇ 誰を 欲するもの何ひとつない
Hey, with whom? With nothing else I desire,
ふたりぼっちの世界でずっと 最後の花火を上げて
in a world where it's just the two of us, forever launching our final fireworks,
フィナーレを飾って 奇跡の古巣 恋に落ちて
gracing our finale, falling in love within the nest of miracles—
誰も話さないで
no one, please don't let go,
呆気ない世界も歩かないで
don't walk through this fleeting world alone.
どんなに恋をしたって 出逢えないよきっと 終わりもない
No matter how much I fall in love, I'll surely never find an end—
幸せに気付こうよ
let's realize this happiness.
Oh my god, I almost cried! I almost cried singing this song!
Thank you for today, guys! Thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zeta because she covered this finale song first, and then I was inspired, so yeah.
あくぼらぎゅねでに... 今日は来てくれて、最後まで見てくれてありがとうございます！
AkuKobo Ragunedesine... Thank you so much for coming today and watching until the very end!
I hope you guys enjoy all the performance, um...
yeah, this whole stream! みんな大好き！ Thank you for your birthday wishes! あとで読んであげますね。うん。
yeah, this whole stream! I love you all! Thank you for your birthday wishes! I'll read them later. Yup.
バイバイみんな！ No more encore! No more encore! バイバイ！
Bye-bye everyone! No more encore! No more encore! Bye-bye!
わこばわこば、こばかないる at your service! Let me hear your send-to shining our day!
Wakoba wakoba, Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me hear your send-to shining our day!
Yo!
Thank you! I can't be as bright as now Without you! Kobo
Thank you! I can't be as bright as now without you!